Finding Aid for the Richard P. Wunder Research Files, 1945-1989 MS.02
The Frick Collection/Frick Art Reference Library Archives
- Series I: Gian Paolo Panini, 1948-1984, 11.0 Linear feet (23 boxes)
  - Subseries 1: Artwork, circa 1948-1960
    - Drawings
      - London (England), British Museum (Box 11, Folder 8-88)
        42 Sketchbook -Man on Horseback, Man with Musket
        43 Sketchbook -Man Seated in Armchair
        44 Sketchbook -Man with a Book
        45 Sketchbook -Man with Bundle and Man on Horseback
        46 Sketchbook -Man with Salver and Eccliastic[sic] [Ecclesiastic]
        47 Sketchbook -Man Bending Forward
        48 Sketchbook -Men Stoning a Fallen Figure
        49 Sketchbook -Monk and Standing Priests
        50 Sketchbook - notes
        51 Sketchbook -Numerous Figure Studies
        52 Sketchbook -Piazza S. Pietro
        53 Sketchbook -Seated and Kneeling Figures
        54 Sketchbook -Seated and Kneeling Men
        55 Sketchbook -Seated and Running Figures
        56 Sketchbook -Seated and Standing Eccliastics[sic] [Ecclesiastics]
        57 Sketchbook -Seated Lady, Drummers
        58-59 Sketchbook -Seated Ladies
        60 Sketchbook -Seated Man
        61 Sketchbook -Seated Man with a Staff
        62 Sketchbook -Seated Men
        63 Sketchbook -Seated Woman
        64 Sketchbook -Sketches of Arms and Monks
        65 Sketchbook -Soldiers and Drummers
        66 Sketchbook -Standing Cavalier
        67 Sketchbook -Standing Cleric and Cornice Molding
        68 Sketchbook -Standing Eccliastic[sic] [Ecclesiastic]
        69-70 Sketchbook -Standing Eccliastics[sic] [Ecclesiastics]
        71 Sketchbook -Standing and Kneeling Men
        72 Sketchbook -Standing, Kneeling and Seated Figure
        73 Sketchbook -Standing Ladies
        74 Sketchbook -Standing Ladies
        75 Sketchbook -Standing Lady
        76 Sketchbook -Standing Lady and Women with a Bucket
        77-80 Sketchbook -Standing Man
        81 Sketchbook -Standing Man and a Hand
        82 Sketchbook -Standing Man and Walking Man
        83 Sketchbook -Standing Man Seen from the Back
        84-88 Sketchbook -Standing Men
      - London (England), British Museum (Box 12, Folder 1-31)
        1 Sketchbook -Standing Men and Cavalier on Horseback
        2 Sketchbook -Standing Men, Benediction Balcony
        3 Sketchbook -Standing Priest and Half-Length Woman
        4 Sketchbook -Standing Woman
        5 Sketchbook -Standing Young Men
        6 Sketchbook -Statuary and Cortile of S. Damaso
        7 Sketchbook -Studies of a Standing Lady and Man with a Gun
        8 Sketchbook -Studies of Bass Fiddler and Drummer
        9 Sketchbook -Studies of Buildings and Coaches
        10 Sketchbook -Studies of Cellists
        11-12 Sketchbook -Studies of Coaches
        13 Sketchbook -Studies of Figures and Carts
        14-15 Sketchbook -Studies of Seated Ladies
        16 Sketchbook -Studies of Seated Ladies and a Man
        17 Sketchbook -Study of a Lady Fanning Herself
        18 Sketchbook -Study of a Man Climbing a Tree
        19 Sketchbook - title page
        20 Sketchbook -Two Figures
        21 Sketchbook -Two Ruffians with a Wine Bottle
        22 Sketchbook -Urn and Statues
        23 Sketchbook -Various Studies of Men
        24 Sketchbook -Walking Gentleman
        25 Sketchbook -Woman with a Basket
        26 Statue, Temples and Arch of Constantine
        27 The Seige of Troy
        28 Two Flying Angels
        29 Two Reclining Male Figures
        30 Urn and Pile of Ruins
        31 Urn, Monument and Ruins
      - London (England), H. M. Calmann -Two Standing Male Figures (Box 12, Folder 32)
      - London (England), Christies (Box 12, Folder 33-34)
        33 Arch of Constantine
        34 Arch of Trajan at Benevento
      - London (England), F. A. Drey -Corinthian Archway, Sibyl Addressing a Group (Box 12, Folder 35)
      - London (England), S. Gahlin collection -Architectural Capriccio (Box 12, Folder 36)
      - London (England), W.R. Jeudwine -Figure Sketches (Box 12, Folder 37)
      - London (England), Nicholson Galleries -Vaulted Structure with Statue of Seated Woman (Box 12, Folder 38)
      - London (England), Royal Institute of British Architects -Baroque Structure (Box 12, Folder 39)
      - London (England), Soane Museum (Box 12, Folder 41-42)
        40 Interior of a Church
        41 Landscape with Ionic Ruins
        42 Landscape with Ruined Arch
      - London (England), Sotheby's -Colosseum (Box 12, Folder 43)
      - London (England), Witt Library (Box 12, Folder 44-49)
        44 Circular Temple, Flaying of Marsyas
        45 Decorations of a Salon
        46 Doric Arcade with Preaching Apostle
        47 Standing Male Figures
        48 Vase, Classical Buildings, Roman Soldiers
        49 Via Sacre, with Arch of Constantine at Left
      - Madrid (Spain), Prado (Box 12, Folder 50-51)
        50 Portico and Truncated Pyramid
        51 Ruined Monument in a Landscape
      - Minneapolis (Minn.), A. M. Clark collection -Ruins (Box 12, Folder 52)
      - Montpellier (France), Musée Alger (Box 12, Folder 53-54)
        53 Cleansing of the Temple
        54 Stoning of Christ
      - Montpellier (France), Musée Fabre -Pile of Ruins (Box 12, Folder 55)
      - New York (N.Y.), Cooper Union Museum (Box 12, Folder 56-57)
        56 Ruined Vaulted Chamber
        57 Ruins
      - New York (N.Y.), Durlacher Brothers (Box 12, Folder 58-59)
        58 Arcade, Statue of Marcus Aurelius
        59 Section of a Frieze
      - New York (N.Y.), Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 12, Folder 60-63)
        60 Belisarius Series
        61 Painted Wall Decoration
        62 Ruined Chamber with Sarcophagus
        63 Ruins with Figure Preaching
      - New York (N.Y.), Pierpont Morgan Library (Box 12, Folder 64-65)
        64 Baroque Ruins and Obelisk
        65 Gothic Ruins
      - New York (N.Y.), Janos Shulz collection -Landscape (Box 12, Folder 66)
      - Northampton (England), Smith College Museum -Death Leap of Marcus Curtius (Box 12, Folder 67)
      - Oxford (England), Ashmolean Museum (Box 12, Folder 68-70)
        68 Sheet of Figure Studies
        69 Statue of Marcus Aurelius and Ruins
        70 Arch of Titus, Colosseum and Ruins
      - Paris (France), M. Carre collection -Stage Set with Baroque Arches (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Paris (France), V. Denon collection -Stairs of the Villa Medici Garden (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Paris (France), Drouot (Box 13, Folder 3-5)
        3 Arch of Janus, Figures Examining a Relief
        4 Circular Temple, Pyramid
        5 Ruined, Vaulted Chamber
      - Paris (France), Ferault -Corinthian Temple in a Landscape (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Paris (France), Louvre (Box 13, Folder 7-33)
        7 Colosseum, Arch of Janus, Lion Attacking Horse Group
        8 Corinthian Portico Hercules and Hydra Group
        9 Corinthian Portico with Fishing Boats
        10 Death Leap of Marcus Curtius
        11 drawings
        12 Five Standing Figures at a Railing
        13 Forum Idealized
        14 Fountain Before Exedra
        15 Four Figures and a Preacher
        16 Obelisk and Arch of Septimius Severus
        17 Opening of the Porta Santa
        18 Portico in a Park
        19 Pyramid, Circular Temple and Torso
        20 Ruined Arcade, Figure Preaching
        21 Ruined Arcade with Statue of Apollo
        22 Ruins of the Baths of Caracalla
        23 Ruins with a Stone Archway
        24 A Sculpted Vase
        25 Three Seated Figures
        26 Study of Rocks
        27 The Tiber and Castel S. Angelo
        28 Tomb of Minerva Medica
        29 Vase Monument Near a Mountain
        30 Vase, Pyramid, Circular Temple
        31 Vestibule of St. Peters
        32 Via del Novicella
        33 View of Side of Temple of Fortuna Virilis
      - Paris (France), unknown -Tomb, Arch and Pyramid (Box 13, Folder 34)
      - Princeton (N.J.), University Art Museum -Ruins (Box 13, Folder 35)
      - Providence (R.I.), John Nicholas Brown -Two Monuments, Caprice (Box 13, Folder 36)
      - Providence (R.I.), Rhode Island School of Design -Arcade, Statue of M. Aurelius (Box 13, Folder 37)
      - Rome (Italy), Duc Heli de Tallyrand -Piazza S. Pietro with a Procession (Box 13, Folder 38)
      - Sacramento (Calif.), Crocker Art Gallery -Temple of Antoninus and Faustina (Box 13, Folder 39)
      - Turin (Italy), Biblioteca Reale -Landscapes (Box 13, Folder 40)
      - Venice (Italy), Accademia -Interior of the Colosseum (Box 13, Folder 41-42)
      - Vienna (Austria), Albertina Gallery (Box 13, Folder 43-54)
        43 Arcade, Apollo Statue and Sarcophagus
        44 Arcade, Statue of the Aged Satyr
        45 Arcade with Figure Addressing Others
        46 The Death Leap of Marcus Curtius
        47 Mass of Ruins, Statue of Hercules and Hydra
        48 Ruined Arcade, Figure Preaching
        49 Ruined Arcade, Statue of Marcus Aurelius
        50 Ruined Palace, Soldier Arousing Others
        51 Ruined Vaulted Chamber, Statue of Athlete
        52 Ruins with a Fountain
        53 Vase and Fountain with Figures
        54 Vaulted Chamber, Statue and Vase
      - Vienna (Austria), G. Nebehay -Arcade, Statue of Female Seated Divinity (Box 13, Folder 55)
      - Windsor Castle (England) (Box 13, Folder 56-58)
        56 Figure with Umbrella Case
        57 Studies of Four Running Figures
        58 Vase and Pile of Ruins
      - Unknown -St. Paul Preaching (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Engravings
      The engravings are arranged alphabetically by title.
      - Arch of Constantine with Figures (Box 13, Folder 60)
      - Arches of Constantine and Janus, Colosseum (Box 13, Folder 61)
      - Aqueduct, Temples of the Sibyl and Fortuna Virilis (Box 13, Folder 62)
      - Arcade with Statue and Figures (Box 13, Folder 63)
      - Concert in Cortile of Palazzo Farnese (Box 13, Folder 64)
      - Figure Addressing a Gathering Before a Temple (Box 13, Folder 65)
      - Figures Discoursing Before A Semi-Circular Arcade (Box 13, Folder 66)
      - Gathering in Cortile of Palazzo Farnese (Box 13, Folder 67)
      - Hadrian's Tomb, Temple of Vespasian (Box 13, Folder 68)
      - Interior of the Pantheon (Box 13, Folder 69-70)
      - Pantheon, Statue of Marcus Aurelius, Column of Trajan (Box 13, Folder 71)
      - Pantheon, Tomb of Minerva Medica, Arch of Constantine (Box 13, Folder 72)
      - Parentalia of M.C. Sobieski (Box 13, Folder 73)
      - Portico with Figure Addressing a Group (Box 13, Folder 74)
      - Preparation for Festival in Piazza Navona (Box 13, Folder 75)
      - Pyramid of Cestius, Colosseum, Column of Trajan (Box 13, Folder 76)
      - Ruins with Figures Conversing (Box 13, Folder 77)
      - Statue of Hermes, Figures Lolling on Ruins (Box 13, Folder 78)
      - Statue, Pyramid, Arch of Janus and Figures (Box 13, Folder 79)
      - Temples of Fortuna Virilis and Concord, Tomb of Hadrian (Box 13, Folder 80)
      - Temples of Saturn and Concord, Arch of Titus (Box 13, Folder 81)
      - Truncated Pyramid Vase with Figures (Box 13, Folder 82)
      - Vaulted Chamber in Ruins, Figures Conversing (Box 13, Folder 83)
      - Vaulted Ruined Chamber, Colosseum, Pantheon (Box 13, Folder 84)
    - Duplicates and Oversize
      - Photostats of Artwork (Duplicates) (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
      - Oversize Photographs and Images, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
        Stored in MS Oversize Box B.
  - Subseries 2: Writings, 1948-1961
    Contains various works that Wunder wrote about Panini during the course of his research. Included are his theses completed for his Bachelor of Arts and Doctor of Philosophy degrees, as well as drafts for various other projects.
    - Giovanni Paolo Panini - Thesis, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      Submitted for BA with Honors, Dept. of Fine Arts, Harvard University. Typed draft with handwritten appendix.
    - Giovanni Paolo Panini - Thesis, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      Typed draft, annotated.
    - Giovanni Paolo Panini - Thesis, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      Typed partial draft on notebook paper, annotated.
    - Giovanni Paolo Panini - Catalog of Works, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      Bound volume, text only, annotated.
    - Giovanni Paolo Panini - Catalog of Works, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Affixed photographs, bound volume, annotated.
    - Giovanni Paolo Panini - Thesis, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Submitted for Doctor of Philosophy in subject of History and Principles of Fine Arts, Harvard. Bound volume.
    - Giovanni Paolo Panini - Thesis, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      Submitted for Doctor of Philosophy in subject of History and Principles of Fine Arts, Harvard. Bound copy.
    - Giovanni Paolo Panini - Plates/Illustrations, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      Bound volume, affixed photographs.
    - Giovanni Paolo Panini - Chronology and Catalog of Works, circa 1950s (Box 18, Folder 2-3)
      Loose pages, marked "extra copy of revised Panini Catalog."
    - Giovanni Paolo Panini - Chronology and Catalog of Works, circa 1950s (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Draft excerpts.
    - Lecture, circa 1950s (Box 19, Folder 2)
      Annotated draft.
    - "Outline of a Proposed Monograph on Giovanni Paolo Panini: His Life, His Works, His Time", circa 1950s (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Various draft excerpts, circa 1950s (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
    - Panini's View of Roman Monuments,Philadelphia Museum of Art Bulletin, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Material removed from volumes, circa 1948-1961 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      Contains correspondence regarding 1949 Harvard degree, notes, one unidentified photograph of two men, and one souvenir matchbook cover.
  - Subseries 3: Correspondence, 1948-1984
    Contains correspondence regarding Wunder's lifelong interest in Panini. The correspondence is organized alphabetically by correspondent.
    - Arisi, Fernando, 1960-1963 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Art Bulletin(Philipp Fehl, Creighton Gilbert), 1967-1970 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Benisovich, Michel N., 1962 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Black, Keith, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Bowron, Edgar Peters (Nelson Atkins Museum), 1979 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Brunetti, Estelle, 1953-1957 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Cleveland Museum of Art (Ann Tzeutschler Lurie, Nancy Loe Wixam), 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Contini-Bonacossi, Conte Alessandro, 1949, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Draper, Robert, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - F. A. Bernett Books, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Feld, Stuart P. (Hirschl and Adler), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Fogg Art Museum, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Frazer, Alfred (Columbia University, Art History and Archaeology), 1974 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Frick Art Reference Library, 1948-1950 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Gabrielli, Noemi, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Gavin, Norman, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Green, Richard, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Honolulu Academy of Arts, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Howard, George, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Juynboll, W.R., 1953-1958 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Leidholm and Co., 1948 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Leitman, Norman (H. Shickman Gallery), 1975 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Librarie Fluory, 1949-1950 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Minneapolis Institute of Arts (Anthony M. Clark), 1966 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Marlin, Robert, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - McCormick, Thomas J., Jr., 1959-1977 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - National Gallery of Art (E. John Bullard), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Newhouse, Clyde (Newhouse Galleries), 1966 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - O'Hara, Clifford Bradley (Clyde Newhouse), 1969 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Osborne, Robert G., 1971 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Parks, Robert O. (Smith College), 1958 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Raydon, Alexander (Raydon Gallery), 1970 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Repetti, Attilio, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Richard Green (Fine Paintings Ltd.), 1968 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Sanguinetti, E.F. (Utah Museum of Fine Arts), 1969 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Serullaz, Maurice (Cabinet du Dessins), 1955 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Silberman, Abris (E. & A. Silberman Gallery), 1951 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Sotheby and Company, 1966-1970 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Stempfle, Felice (Pierpont Morgan Library), 1969 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Sternberg, Maurice, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Trianon Foundation (John W. Metzger), 1964 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - The Van Dieman Galleries, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Wadsworth Atheneum, 1956 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Willard, Helen D., 1968 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Wolf, Emile, 1965-1970 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Wunder, Katherine, undated (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Young, Chloe H. (Allen Memorial Art Museum), 1969 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - "Correspondence on works of which I have no photo", 1948-1963 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Subseries 4: Research Material, circa 1948-1980s
    Contains bibliographies, auction catalogs, and various notes that relate to Wunder's Panini research.
    - Artwork influenced by Panini, circa 1950s (Box 21, Folder 1)
      Contains photographs, provenance notes, and correspondence regarding paintings, wallpaper decorations, etc. that are similar to Panini's work.
    - Auction catalog excerpts and notes, 1960s-1980s (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Auction Sales Lists, circa 1950s (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Bibliographies, circa 1950s (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Catalog of Paintings in the Gallery of Cardinal Valenti, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Criticism of Panini (notes), circa 1950s (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Interiors of Rooms, circa 1950s (Box 21, Folder 7)
      Contains notes, publications, clippings, and photographs.
    - Notebooks, circa 1950s (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Note cards for Catalog of Works, circa 1950s (Box 21, Folder 9)
      Located in Note Card Box 1.
    - Notes, circa 1950s (Box 21, Folder 10-12)
    - Notes, circa 1950s (Box 21b, Folder 1)
    - Photoreproduction, circa 1948-1955 (Box 21b, Folder 2)
      Contains invoices, receipts, correspondence, notes.
  - Subseries 5: Printed Material, circa 1950s-1970s
    Contains printed publications collected by Wunder that relate to Panini. Includes articles published in 1921, 1926, 1939, and 1940.
    - Arisi, Fernando.Gian Paolo Panini, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
      Folder 2 contains inserted material removed from the volume (critical notes about the text by Richard Wunder).
    - Olsen, Harald. "Et Malet Galleri af Pannini: Kardinal Silvio Valenti Gonzagas Semling", 1951 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Ozzola, Leandro. "Aggiunte al Panini,"Strenna, XVIII, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Ozzola, Leandro. "Nuove Aggiunte al Panini," reprint, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Ozzola, Leandro, "Gian Paolo Pannini: Pittore,", 1921 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Peat, Wilbur D., "Two Paintings of Roman Monuments by Panini,"Bulletin of the Art Association of Indianapolis, Indiana, XXXVII, 1950 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Valeri, Francesco Malagazzi, "I Pannini de Museo Civico di Piancenza,"Strenna Piacentina., 1926 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Auction Catalogs, 1950s-1970s (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
      Several oversize catalogs stored in MS Oversize Box B.
- Series II: Hyacinth Rigaud, 1950-1987, 10.0 Linear feet (20 boxes)
  The Hyacinth Rigaud material was created and collected by a colleague of Wunder's, George Van Derveer Gallenkamp. Wunder received Gallenkamp's extensive research files regarding Rigaud as a bequest. The bulk of the material consists of artwork files containing photographs, provenance information, and correspondence. Also included are Gallenkamp's writings on the topic of Rigaud, including various articles, his thesis, and the beginnings of a catalogue raisonn├®. Additionally, the series contains correspondence, subject files, printed material, notes and other research material. Various Gallenkamp material not related to Rigaud is found at the end of the series.
  - Subseries 1: Artwork, circa 1950s-1970s
    Artwork files are arranged alphabetically by city. This arrangement reflects the location of Rigaud works at the time of Gallenkamp's research. Each folder contains material regarding one or more works by Rigaud located in that particular city. The files may contain photographs, correspondence, notes, or a combination.
    - Aix-en-Provence, France (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Albi, France (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Alger, Algeria (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Baltimore, Md. (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Basel, Switzerland (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Besancon, France (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Boston, Mass. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Bourg, France (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Bourges, France (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Bourgoin, France (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Caen, France (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Cambrai, France (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Cambridge, Mass. (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Carcassonne, France (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Carlsruhe, Germany (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Champlatreaux, France (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Chartres, France (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Chenonceau, France (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Cher, France (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Cherbourg, France (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Chicago, Ill. (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Clermont, France (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Cleveland, Ohio (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Cologne, Germany (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Copenhagen, Denmark (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Dallas, Texas (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Dartmouth, England (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Detroit, Mich. (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Dijon, France (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Darmstadt, Germany (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Dunkerque, France (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - El Paso, Texas (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Enfield, N.H. (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Florence, Italy (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Fontenay, France (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Fredericksburg, Denmark (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Geneva, Switzerland (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Genoa, Italy (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Hamburg, Germany (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Langres, France (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Le Puy, France (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - London, England (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Los Angeles, Calif. (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Louisville, Ky. (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Lyon, France (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Madrid, Spain (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Manchester, England (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Marseilles, France (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Meikleour, Scotland (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Melbourne, Australia (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Mende, France (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Monaco (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Montpellier, France (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Moravia, Czech Republic (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Nantes, France (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Narbonne, France (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - New Orleans, La. (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - New York, N.Y. (Box 25, Folder 17-18)
    - Nimes, France (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Northampton, England (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Orleans, France (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Ottowa, Canada (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Paris, France (Box 26, Folder 2-4)
    - Perpignan, France (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Philadelphia, Pa. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Providence, R.I. (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Raleigh, N.C. (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Reno, Nev. (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Rodez, France (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Rouen, France (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - St. Germain, France (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Sacramento, Calif. (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - San Francisco, Calif. (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Saumur, France (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Stockholm, Sweden (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Stockton, England (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Syracuse, N.Y. (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Toulouse, France (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Tours, France (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Valence, France (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Valenciennes, France (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Versailles, France (Box 27, Folder 5-8)
    - Vienna, Austria (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Washington, D.C. (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Welbeck Abbey, England (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Williamstown, Mass. (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Windsor Castle, England (Box 27, Folder 13)